Guide to the Science Fiction and Comic Fanzine Collection, 1952-2005 SC.1980.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Comic Fanzines, 1952-2005; I.
  - Paragon Illustrated, 1969-1972; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Published in Tallahassee, FL and edited by William F. Schwartz and William Black.
  - People's Comic Book Newsletter, 1995-2005; 4 issues (Box 5, Folder 23-24)
    Published in Elk Grove, CA by Jazma Universe Online and edited by Paul Dale Roberts.
  - Pittsburgh Comix Club Bulletin, 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA by the Pittsburgh Comix Club and edited by Benjamin Pondexter.
  - Pittsburgh Fan Forum, 1975-1976; 9 issues (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA by the Pittsburgh Comix Club and edited by Mark Lerer.
  - Quintessence, 1973; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Published in Spokane, WA and edited by Johnny Achziger.
  - The Robert Kline Portfolio, 1972; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Rocket's Blast Comicollector, 1964-1980; 76 issues (Box 6, Folder 1-10, Box 5, Folder 29-36)
    Published in Miami, FL and San Diego, CA by the SFCA and edited by G.B. Love AKA Gordon B. Love and James Van Hise.
  - Rocket's Blast Special, 1967; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sense of Wonder, 1972; 3 issues (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Published in Lewiston, ID and edited by Doug Potter and Bill Schnelly.
  - Sonic, 1966; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Published in Fort Wayne, IN and edited by Larry Goltz.
  - Strip Scene, 1977-1980; 13 issues (Box 5, Folder 14-16)
    Published in Alberta, Canada and edited by Carl Horak.
  - Strips, 1977-1978; 4 issues (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Published in Auckland, New Zealand and edited by Rollo Treadway.
  - This Magazine, 1974; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Published in Toronto, Ontario, Canada and edited by Satu Repo.
  - Tony Isabella Presents, 1972; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Published in Cleveland, OH and edited by Tony Isabella.
  - Udenlandske Tegneserier (Foreign Comics), 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Franco-Belgian comics.
  - Vancouver Comic Book Club (VCBC) Bulletin, 1980; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Published in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada and edited by Jay O'Keefe.
  - The Vault of Mindless Fellowship, 1972; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Published in Madison, WI and edited by Bruce Ayres and Steven Grant.
  - Wise Up, 1974-1976; 3 issues (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Published in Minneapolis, MN by the MCFA and edited by David Mruz and Larry Becker.
  - The Wonderful World of Marvel, 1976; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Published in Rockville, MD and edited by Steve Hauk and Doug Fratz.
  - Wonderworld, 1973; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - The World of Comic Art, 1966; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Published in Hawthorne, CA and edited by Dorothy McGreal.
  - Wow, 1966; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Published in Tampa, FL and edited by Dan Wicker.
  - Woweekazowie, 1976-1978; 2 issues (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Published in Acton, MA and edited by William A. Blyberg.
  - Xenophile, 1975-1977; 6 issues (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Published in St. Louis, MO and edited by Nils Hardin.
  - Yesteryear, 1980; 1 issue (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Published in Princeton, WI and edited by Dennis Kitchen and Mike Jacobi.
- Science Fiction Fanzines, 1966-1982; II.
  This series includes science fiction fanzines created between 1964 and 1980 by national and local individuals, organizations, and clubs. The series is organized alphabetically and when possible, the publication information, including location, publisher and editors(s) are noted in the scope and content notes.
  - Adrienne APA-LOC, 3 issues (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Published in White Plains, NY and edited by Adrienne Fein.
  - The Adventures of Superfein, 1978-1979; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Airfoil, 1978; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Published in New Rochelle, NY and edited by Arthur D. Hlavaty.
  - Airfoiled Yarmulka, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - The Alien Critic, 1974; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Published in Portland, OR and edited by Richard E. Geis. Title later changed to Science Fiction Review.
  - All About Star Trek Fanclubs, 1976; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Published by Ego Enterprises of New York, Inc. in New York, NY and edited by Tony Tallarico.
  - Alvega, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Published in Elmont, NY and edited in Alyson L. Abramowitz.
  - An Art Folio by Frazetta, Wood, Crandall, Williamson, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - APA-H: Amateur Press Association for Hoaxes, 1978-1979; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Edited by Harry J. N. Andruschak.
  - Arceibo, 1978; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Likely edited by Tony Trull.
  - Artifact, 1979; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Published in Dunbar, PA by the Actors and Artists of Fayette Country, Inc.
  - Australian Science Fiction Review, 1966-1967; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Published in Melbourne, Australia and edited by John Bangsund.
  - Bastard of Grafan, 1973; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Published in St. Louis, MO and edited by De'V Hanke.
  - Boris, 1978; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Published and edited by Mark A. Feldman and John A. Taylor in Silver Spring, MD. Features the art of Boris Vallejo.
  - Bosh, 1969; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Published in New York state.
  - Brassor, 1978-1979; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Published in Ann Arbor, MI and edited by Marty L. Levine.
  - Breet, 1971-1972; 4 issues (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Published in New York state and edited by David Emerson.
  - Cerebrum, 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Published in Yonkers, NY and edited by M. Goldfarb and K. Bornstein.
  - Close Encounters of the GHL III Kind, 1978; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Collage, 10 issues (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Published in Miami, FL and edited by G.B. Love.
  - Collapse, 1978; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Published in Houston, TX and edited by Robert O. Welling.
  - Contact, 1973; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Published in Baltimore, MD as the newsletter for the Philadelphia Bidding Committee.
  - Convention: News for Convention Planners, 1969; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Andrew I. Porter.
  - Cosmic Reflections, 1977; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by John Persky for the Taylor Allderice Science Fiction and Comix Club.
  - Cosmos, 1977; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by David G. Hartwell.
  - Cover, 1971-1978; 6 issues (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Jeff Schalles.
  - Critical Mass, 1978; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Published in East Providence, RI and edited by Don D'Ammassa.
  - Crossroads, 1970; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Edited by Al Snider for the Brown University Science Fiction Union.
  - Cullowhee Comments, 1978-1979; 3 issues (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Published in Cullowhee, NC and edited by Richard Llewllyn.
  - Curious Eyre, 1977; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Published in Chicago, IL and edited by Dennis Jarog, AKA The Great Bird.
  - Cusfussing, 3 issues (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Charles Seelig for the Barnard-Columbia Science Fiction Society.
  - Cycle, 1969; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Published in Kansas City, MI and edited by Ravi Kristin and Art Wilson for Underground Central, a subsidary of Kirstin-Wilson & Stuff, a subsidary of the Freehold Foundation of the Church of All Worlds.
  - Cygnus X-1, 1975; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Bob Ruben for the Western Pennsylvania Science Fiction Association.
  - Dark Horizons, 1975-1977; 6 issues (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Published in Birmingham, UK and edited by Stephen Jones for the British Fantasy Society.
  - Darkover Newsletter, 1977; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Published in Berkeley, CA and edited by Ted Bryan for the Friends of Darkover.
  - Day-Glo Telegraph, 1972; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Edited by David Emerson and Janet Kagan.
  - Debris, 1979; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by John Boston.
  - Delap's Fantasy & Science Fiction Review, 1976-1978; 13 issues (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
    Published in Culver City, CA and edited by Richard Delap.
  - Diagonal Relationship, 1977-1980; 10 issues (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Published in New Rochelle, NY and edited by Arthur D. Hlavaty and Adrienne Fein.
  - Double Bill, 1966-1967; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 41)
    Published in Akron, OH and edited by Bill Mallardi, William L Bowers, and Earl E. Evers.
  - Drift, 1975; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Gary Farder.
  - Eli Among The Ice Floes or, Never Give A Saga An Even Break, 1974; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 43)
    Published in Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada.
  - Empire, 1967-1968; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 44)
    Published in Albany, NY and edited by Mark J. McGarry.
  - Famous Fantastic Adventures, 1971; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Published in Wilson, NC and edited by John G. Clayton.
  - Fan Informer: The FFCG Newszine, 1973; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 46)
    Edited by Joe Wesson.
  - Fangoria, 1979; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 47)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Joe Bonham. By Starlog.
  - Fanhistorica, 1975; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 48)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Joe D. Siclari and Gary Farber.
  - Fantasy Amateur, 1979; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Fantasy Classics, 1973; 3 issues (Box 7, Folder 50)
    Published in North Hollywood, CA and edited by Ken Krueger.
  - Fantasy Crossroads, 1977-1978; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 51)
    Published in Hurst, Texas and edited by Jonathan Bacon.
  - Fantasy Unlimited, 1977; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Published in Freeport, NY and edited by Frank Veripapa.
  - Feinzine, 1978-1979; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - File 770, 1978; 7 issues (Box 7, Folder 54)
    Published in Sylmar, CA and edited by Mike Glyer.
  - File Forty, 1974; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 55)
    Published by the United Network Command for Law and Enforcement and edited by Craig Henderson.
  - For Your Eyes Only, 1973-1975; 9 issues (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Published by Intelligence and Communications: Section 4, United Network Command for Law and Enforcement in Bowie, MD and edited by Craig Henderson.
  - Foundation, 1975-1978; 5 issues (Box 7, Folder 57)
    Published in Nottingham, UK and edited by Peter Nicholls.
  - Francis X. Cheep Cheep, 1978-1979; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 58)
    Published by the Johnstown, PA located Chipmunk Press while away at conventions. 1978 issue is unspecified, 1979 issue was printed at Seacon 1979.
  - Frost in August, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 59)
    Published in Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada and edited by Eli Cohen.
  - Fugitive, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Future Focus, 1978; 2 issues (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Edited by Reed Richmond and Roger Reynolds for the Findlay College Science Fiction Club.
  - Garden Ghouls Gazette, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 62)
    Edited by Dave T. Keil.
  - Golden Apple, 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Gobrin Gazette, 1976; 1 issue (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Gosh Wow!, 1969; 3 issues (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Granfalloon, 1968-1976; 12 issues (Box 7, Folder 66, Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Linda Eyster AKA Linda E. Bushyager, Suzanne Tompkins and Ron Bushyager.
  - Guying Gyre, 1978; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Published in Hawthorne, CA and edited by Gil Gaier for Hawthorne High School.
  - HAPA Ask Not, 1976; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Barbara Geraud.
  - Holier Than Thou, 1976; 4 issues (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Published in North Hollywood, CA and edited by Marty Cantor.
  - Honor To Finuka, 1979; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Published in Riverside, CA and edited by Kurt Cockrum and Martha Koester.
  - Hopsfanatic, 1975; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Published in Baltimore, MD and edited by Charles Hamilton and Tim Daniels for the Hopkins Science Fiction Association.
  - HPL: A Tribute to Howard Phillips Lovecraft, 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Published in Birmingham, AL and edited by Meade and Penny Frierson.
  - I Promised, 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Incompleat Filksinger (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Infinite Dreams, 1975-1978; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Published in Kent, OH and edited by Clint Johnson and Tom Moldvay.
  - Infinity, 1972-1973; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Published in New York and Astoria, NY and edited by Gary Berman, Adam Malin and Joe Rizzo.
  - Introducing James Branch Cabell, 1970; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Published by the James Branch Cabell Society in Oradell, NJ and edited by James Blish and William Leigh Godshalk.
  - Invisible Fan, 1978-1979; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Published in Kensington, MD and edited by Avedon Carol.
  - Janus, 1977-1978; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Published in Madison, WI and edited by Janie Bogstad and Jeanne Gomoll.
  - JDMBibliophile, 1979-1980; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 16)
    A John D. MacDonald zine. Edited by Ed Hirshberg.
  - John Chance Vs. Dread: The Apocalypse, 1975; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Published in Columbus, OH and edited by Gary Hoppenstand.
  - Journey-Zine, 1975; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Anthony Deen.
  - Karass, 1974-1978; 10 issues (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Published in Prospect Park, PA and edited by Linda Bushyager.
  - Khatru, 1977; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Published in Baltimore, MD and edited by Jeffrey D. Smith.
  - Kickshaw, 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Published in Seattle, WA and edited by Clifford R. Wind.
  - Kolvir, 1975; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Published in Baltimore, MD and edited by Tim Daniels for The Amber Society at Johns Hopkins University.
  - Kratophany, 1971-1975; 7 issues (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Published in New York state and edited by Eli Cohen.
  - Lan's Lantern, 1977-1978; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Published in Bloomfield Hills, MI and edited by George J. Laskowski Jr. AKA Lan.
  - Lasfapa, 1977-1978; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Published in Studio City, CA and edited by Marty Cantor for the Los Angeles' Scientifiction Fans' Amateur Press.
  - Liberated Quark, 1977-1978; 2 issues (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Published in Newport News, VA and edited by M.E. Tyrrell and George Beahm. for the Hamption Roads Science Fiction Association.
  - Lift Off, 1978; 3 issues (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Published in Nashville, TN and edited by Perry Glen Moore.
  - Lines of Occurrence, 1980; 1 issue (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Locus, 1968-1971; 170 issues (Box 8, Folder 29-35)
    Published in the Bronx, NY and edited by Charlie and Marsha Brown. Includes surveys and supplement issue.
  - Luna Monthly, 1969-1977; 64 issues (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
    Published in Oradell, NJ and edited by Ann F. Dietz and Frank Dietz.
  - Madstar Science Fiction Quarterly, 1971; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Published in Alexandria, VA and edited by Robert Lewis.
  - Maelstorm, 1979; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Michael Cain and Greg Mosby.
  - Maine(ly) Trek, 1979; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Published in Lewistown, Me and edited by Lizette R. Leveille.
  - Mandolin Picks, Perhaps, 1974; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Published in Medfor, MA and edited by Morris M. Keesan.
  - Matroid, 1975; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Tom Morley.
  - Maya, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Published in Newcastle upon Tyne, UK and edited by Robert Jackson.
  - Maybe, 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Published in Chattanooga, TN and edited by Irvin Koch.
  - Media Five Magazine, 1975; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Published in London, Ontario, Canada and edited by Bill Chankh.
  - Meeper Blue, 9 issues (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Published in Eerie, PA and edited by George Paczolt, Jr.
  - Men, Halflings & Hero Worship, 1973; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Published in Baltimore, MD. Written by Marion Zimmer Bradley.
  - Metasex Madness, 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Published in New Rochelle, NY and edited by Rev. Arthur Daniel Hlavaty.
  - Midnight Sun, 1974; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Published in Columbus, Ohio. Written by Karl Edward Wagner and edited and published by Gary Hoppenstand.
  - The Mimeo Man, 1975; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 17)
    "A faanish musical by Moshe Feder, Debbie Notkin, Eli Cohen." Performed at the 1974 PgHLANGE and 1975 Disclave. Published by Panacea Press Publications.
  - Mini-Demons, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Edited by Bob Tinnell.
  - The Miscast Barbarian, 1975; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 19)
    "A biography of Robert E. Howard (1906-1936) by L. Sprague de Camp." Published by Gerry de la Ree in Saddle River, NJ.
  - Mixed Company, 5 issues (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Edited by Beth Schwarzin. Contains many zines submitted by different people.
  - Mongoose, 1978; 7 issues (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Published in Honolulu and edited by Seth Goldberg and Leslie Blitman for the Honolulu Science Fiction Soeciety.
  - Monolith, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Published in Ukiah, CA and edited by Dave Mitchell.
  - Monsters and Heroes, 1967-1979; 6 issues (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Published in New York, NY by M and H Publications. Features the work of Larry Ivie.
  - Multilog, 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Mythlore, 1970; 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Published by the Mythopoeic Society in Maywood, CA and edited by Glen GoodKnight.
  - Mythologies, 1977-1978; 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Published in East Providence, RI and edited by Don and Sheila D'Ammassa.
  - The NESFA Hymnal, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Published by the New England Science Fiction Association, Inc. in Cambridge, MA.
  - Newspaper of Science Fiction and Fantasy, 1977; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY.
  - Niekas, 1966; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Edmund R. Maskys and Felice Rolfe.
  - Nightspawn, 1972; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Published in Detroit, MI and edited by Alex Marciniszyn and Kevin Siembieda.
  - The Northumberland Dispatch, 1978; 3 issues (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Published by the Fifth Northumberland Fusiliers and edited by Jean Weidner.
  - Noumenon, 1978-1979; 7 issues (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Published in New Zealand and edited by Brian Thurogood.
  - NTM Collected, 1978; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Published in Nurray, KY and edited by Jean Lorrah.
  - Nyctalops, 1970; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Published in Albuquerque, NM and edited by Harry O. Morris, Jr. and Edward P. Berglund.
  - Oak Leaves, 1970-1972; 7 issues (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Published in St. Michael, ND and edited by David Anthony Kraft.
  - Obscure, 1975; 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Published in Port Jefferson, NY and edited by Glenn Jeffrey Marcus.
  - Odyssey, 1976; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Roger Elwood.
  - O'Ryann, 1970; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 38)
    "A portfolio of sketches from the Steranko Masterwork O'Ryann's Odyssey." Published by Supergraphics.
  - Other Places, Other Times, 1976; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Published in Cleveland, OH and edited by Mike Glicksohn with art by Randall Bathurst.
  - Outworlds, 1974; 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 40)
    Published in Wadsworth, OH and edited by Bill and Joan Bowers.
  - Overflow, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Published in Roanoke, VA
  - Paradox, 1973; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Published in Montreal, Canada and edited by Robert Bruce Robbins.
  - Perihelion Science Fiction, 1967-1978; 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Sam Bellotto, Jr. and Eric M. Jones for the Brooklyn Center, Long Island University.
  - The Perry Rhodan Fanzine, 1974; 4 issues (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Published in New Bedford, MA and edited by Mike Botelho.
  - Pghoenix, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Published in Library, PA and edited by Marvin D. Kilmer.
  - The Phantasy Review, 1973; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 46)
    Published in Sioux Falls, SD and edited by William Reynolds and Devid Fryxell.
  - Phosphene, 1978; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Published in Torrance, CA and edited by Gil Gaier.
  - Photon, 1972; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Mark Frank.
  - The Pickled Goldfish, 1978; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Published in South Windsor, CT and edited by Timothy Roaix AKA The Dark Barbarian.
  - Portal, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 50)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Henry Roll.
  - Procrastination, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 51)
    Published in Strafford, PA and edited by Darrell Schweitzer.
  - The Proper Boskonian, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 52)
    Published in Cambridge, MA and edited by Richard Harter.
  - Pulp, 1978; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 53)
    Edited and published by Robert Weinberg in Chicago, IL.
  - Purient Interest, 1971; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 54)
    The official organ of BRUNSFFA.
  - Quark, 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 55)
    Published in Arnold, MS and edited by Lesleigh and Chris Couch.
  - Quibble, 1976; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 56)
    A collection of fanzines by different authors.
  - Quinapulus, 1979; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 57)
    Published in Minneapolis, MN and edited by M.K. Digre.
  - Raki, 1967; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 58)
    Edited by M.G. Zaharakis and Laura.
  - Real Soon Now, 1967; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 59)
    Published in Chevy Chase, MD and edited by Banks Mebane.
  - REH: Lone Star Fictioneer, 1975; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 60)
    Published in Shawnee Mission, Kansas and edited by Byron L. Roark and Arnold M. Fenner.
  - Replay, 1978; 2 issues (Box 9, Folder 61)
    Published in Lake Jackson, TX and edited by Joanne Burger.
  - The Revised H.P. Lovecraft Bibliography, 1973; 1 issue (Box 9, Folder 62)
    By Mark O. Wings with Jack L. Chalker. Published by the Mirage Press, ltd in Baltimore, MD.
  - Riverside Quarterly, 1964-1977; 24 issues (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    Published in Iowa City, IA and edited by Leland Sapiro.
  - Rune, 1969-1980; 8 issues (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Published in Minneapolis, MN and edited by Jim Young, Lee Pelton and Carol Kennedy.
  - Science-Fiction Collector, 1976-1977; 5 issues (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Published in Calgary, Alberta, Canada and edited by James Grant Thiessen.
  - Science Fiction and Fantasy Book Review, 1979; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Published in San Bernardino, CA and edited by R. Reginald.
  - Science Fiction Review, 1975-1979; 17 issues (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
    Published in Portland, OR and edited by Richard E. Geis.
  - Science Fiction Review Monthly, 1975-1976; 4 issues (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Brian Dougal and Martin Last.
  - Scientifriction, 1977; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Scifire!, 1978; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Published in Milwaukee, WI and edited by Jimi Higgins for University of Wisconsin – Milwaukee Science Fiction Services.
  - Seldon Seen, 1967; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Sam Bellotto, Jr. for the Harry Seldon Foundation Society.
  - Seraphim, 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Published in Waterville, MA and edited by Thomas Velleux.
  - SF Bibliodd: Newsletter for the UMBC Science Fiction Collection, 1974; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Published in Baltimore, MD and edited by Steve Miller.
  - SF Bibliographies, 1972; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 15)
    "An annotated bibliography of bibliographical works on science fiction and fantasy fiction." Published by Advent Publishers, Inc. in Chicago, IL and edited by Robert E. Briney and Edward Wood.
  - Sirius, 1977; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Published in Audubon, NJ and edited by Ed Chambers.
  - Skyworlds, 1977-1978; 4 issues (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Published in Rockville Centre, NY.